Finding Aid for the Harold Stirling Vanderbilt Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY, HARVARD: (Box 2., Folder 9.)
  - HSV, photographed beside Commodore statue, 11x14", 1964 (3 photos, 1 mounted) (Box 2., Folder 9.)
  - Harvard Medical School, Vanderbilt Hall (6 mounted photos) (Box 2., Folder 9.)
- GERTRUDE CONAWAY VANDERBILT: (Box 3., Folder Folder 2.)
- Camp (Box 3., Folder Folder 1.)
- Miscellaneous-trips, sports, tennis, swimming, groups (Box 3., Folder Folder 2.)
- Early 1900's, including travel (Box 3., Folder Folder 3.)
- Tintypes (Box 3., Folder Folder 4.)
- Gertrude C. Vanderbilt, early photographs (Box 3., Folder Folder 5.)
- " " (Box 3., Folder Folder 6.)
- Gertrude C. Vanderbilt, family (Box 3., Folder Folder 7.)
- Horses, wedding party (Box 3., Folder Folder 8.)
- Early'1900's, groups, schools, parties (Box 3., Folder Folder 9.)
- Farm (Box 3., Folder Folder 10.)
- Farm (Box 3., Folder Folder 10.)
- UNIDENTIFIED (Box 4.)
  - Snapshots-groups, family members, homes, boats, ttrips (Box 4.)
  - PHOTO ALBUM, Gertrude C. Vanderbilt, 11 x 15" Family photos, early 20th century - 1920's, trips Oxford, Paris, France, Scotland Italy, horses (Box 4.)
  - PHOTO ALBUM, Gertrude C. Vanderbilt, 5% x 8%" Portraits, family groups, dogs (Box 4.)
- HSVIN
Social Work 12/10/54 TNSSW Newsletter Page 3 Article about Mrs. Mary Jane Werthan Page 3 Article about Mrs. Mary Jane Werthan
Robson, Vera Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 3/29/61 (3)
Roosevelt, George E. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 5/1/60 (3)
Roosevelt, Julian K. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 1/10/61 (3)
Sanborn, Wayne A. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 6/24/64 (3)
Scribner, Charles, Jr. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 6/1/64 (3)
Silk, George Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 6/13/67 (3)
Stephens, Olin J., II Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 10/26/56 (3)
Stephens, Roderick, Jr. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 3/29/41 (3)
Stephens, Roderick, II Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 4/3/41 (3)
Stewart, W.A.W. North Amer. Yacht Racin 1 Yachting 11/17/59 (3)
Gilreath, Harold L. Stewart, W.A.W. 1 Yachting 11/3/59 (3)
Stewart, W.A.W. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 11/27/59 (3)
Stewart, W.A.W. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 12/7/59 (3)
Stewart, W.A.W. North Amer.Yacht Racin 1 Yachting 1/5/60 (3)
Stewart, W.A.W. Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 5/31/60 (3)
Sunceville, Hugh Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 2/28/63 (3)
Valenzuela, Mario Vanderbilt, Harold S. 2 Yachting 7/31/67 9/8/67 (3)
Ware, J. Herbert Vanderbilt, Harold S. 3 Yachting 4/9/60 5/18/63 (3)
Curley, Rosemary Vanderbilt, Harold S. 1 Yachting 8/26/64 (3)
Claiborne, J. T., Jr. Beha, James J. 1 Business 1/12/71 (2)
Beha, James J. Claiborne, J. T., Jr. 1 Business 10/19/70 (2)
Claiborne, J. T., Jr. Beha, James J. 1 Business 10/15/70 (2)
Library of Congress, Cop Lewis, Sol 1 Business 8/13/70 (2)
Beha, James J. Claiborne, J. T., Jr. 1 Business 10/7/70 (2)
Claiborne, J. T., Jr. Beha, James J. 1 Business 9/25/70 (2)
Heil, Henry F. Koenig, John 1 Business 10/10/70 (3)
Claiborne, J. T., Jr. Beha, James J. 1 Business 8/17/70 (2)
Beha, James J. Claiborne, J. T., Jr. 1 Business 8/13/70 (2)
Claiborne, J. T., Jr. Beha, James J. 1 Business 8/3/70 (2)
Teague, W. Dorwin Vanderbilt, Gertrude 1 Business 7/20/70 (3)
Vanderbilt, William H. Teague, W. Dorwin 1 Business 7/16/70 (3)
Teague, W. Dorwin Vanderbilt, William H. 1 Business 7/13/70 (3)
Faulds, Captain Vanderbilt, Gertrude 1 Business 10/10/71 (2)
Engles, Richard E. Vanderbilt, Gertrude 1 Business 10/12/71 (2)
Fleming, C. C. Vanderbilt, Gertrude 1 Business 12/21/71 (2)
Engles, Richard E. Vanderbilt, Harold & Gert 1 Business 6/29/72 (2)
Burley, Richard W. Beha, James J. 1 Vanderbilt 2/14/73 (2)
Burley, Richard W. Beha, James J. 1 Vanderbilt 2/19/73 (2)
Sunny Beha, James J. 1 Business 2/19/73 (3)
Beha, James J. Burley, P. Leslie 1 Vanderbilt 2/8/73 (2)
Beha, James J. Vanderbilt, William H. 1 Vanderbilt 2/8/73 (2)
Beha, James J. Vanderbilt, Alfred G. & M 1 Vanderbilt 2/8/73 (2)